





Summary

Jump to Section

Enthusiastic Software Engineer having 1-year experience in IT and eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail, and excellent organizational and SDLC skills. Motivated to learn, grow, and excel in the IT industry.

Work Experience

• as -

Jan 2021 to Till Date

• ABS Professional Services India Private Limited as TRAINEE PRODUCT DEVELOPER Jun 2017 to Feb 2018

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Designed new product elements such as continuous database monitoring, for raising high data loads.

Developed system UI dashboard using Angular 4.0

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Walchand College of eng. Sangli in 2017

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:
Winner Of Techno Champ
Business Analysis Foundations: Business Process Modeling
SEO for Social Media
The Complete Digital Marketing Course - 12 Courses in 1
Angular- Essential Training
SQL essential training

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Python	3.9.0	2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
1 0 : 1	405	0000	0.14 () 0.84 (1/)

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

JavaScript	1.8.5	2020	2 Year(s) 2 Month(s)
Numpy, SciPy, MatPlotlib		2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
NLTK		2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Oracle, MongoDB, Cassandra		2019	1 Year(s)
Elasticsearch		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
UI/UX, Web Development		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
JAVA	15.0.1	2019	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
C,C++		2019	2 Year(s) 3 Month(s)
Angular	10	2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert		✓	

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Citizen's Help & Complaint App

Client: Personal Project

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Sep 2020 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: app for registering incident, complaint or seek help to and from government officials for all citizens.

Project Title: Contact Management Web App

Client: Personal Project

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jul 2020 - Sep 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Angularjs, Node.Js, Javascript,

Project Details: Made easy to search contacts & edit them in angular web app.

Project Title: Read SMS App

Client: Personal Project

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Aug 2019 - Mar 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Python,

Project Details: Reduced the user time to read OTP from SMS using text to voice

interface.

Project Title: Personalized News App

Client: Personal Project

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Python, Machine Learning,

Project Details: Developed an unsupervised web scraping app to extract news article

content independent of underlying HTML structure.

Project Title: Databse Monitor

Client: ABS Services (India) Private Limited Nature of Employment: Full Time

Role: Programmer

Duration: Jun 2017 - Mar 2018

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 3

Skill Used: Java, Angularjs,

Role Description: Developed the site for live monitoring of traffic on databases.

Project Details: Monitored the live traffic on databases of ABS

Project Title: Digi Vote

Client: WCE, Sangli.

Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Project Leader

Duration: Oct 2016 - Apr 2017 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 4

Skill Used: Java, Android,

Project Details: Implemented Aadhaar UID, fingerprint & OTP based secure-digital

voting system to increase voting percentage in India.

Project Title: Augment Shopee Client: WCE, Sangli.

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Role: Programmer

Duration: Jan 2016 - Jun 2016

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 3

Skill Used: Unity3D, C#,

Role Description: Developed android app in Unity3d

Project Details: Personalized shopping experiences for home by providing 3D furniture

model by augmenting experience of new furniture in home.

www.youtube.com/watch?v=8eL2Nx13e8g

Project Title: Sulabh Kheti

Client: Jonn Deer Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Programmer

Duration: Aug 2015 - Jul 2016 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 3

Skill Used: Python, Machine Learning, Html5, Bootstrap, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Role Description: ML based classification & Web Development. Project Details: IOT & ML based irrigation automation & recommendation system for farmers, to select most favorable and profitable crops during a particular period

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Category: SC

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.